[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is a natural healing method that uses the reflex points of the feet, which correspond to different organs and areas of the body.", "correct_answer": "Reflexology", "incorrect_answers": ["Oriental Massage Therapy", "Aromatherapy Massage", "Relaxation Massage"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In trigonometry this law, which generalizes the Pythagorean theorem, is a statement about a general triangle, which relates the lengths of its sides to the cosine of a known angle.", "correct_answer": "The Law of Cosines", "incorrect_answers": ["The Archimedean Principle", "The Law of Adjacent Hypotenuses", "The Rule of Three"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There is an intact dodo egg specimen housed in the East London museum in South Africa.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name for all the chemical reactions that take place in the body?", "correct_answer": "metabolism", "incorrect_answers": ["nutrition", "absorption", "digestion"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The all-pro defensive tackle from the Detroit Lions, Alex Karras, played the role of Porky in the 1982 film Porkys.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If you and I are chatting over the Internet and I write LOL, that means that I am doing this.", "correct_answer": "Laughing", "incorrect_answers": ["Crying", "Sleeping", "Eating"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He invented the idea of an ATM in the late 1930s and persuaded what is now Citicorp to give it a trial.", "correct_answer": "Luther George Simjian", "incorrect_answers": ["James Goodfellow", "Allen Bred", "John Shepherd-Barron"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Kismet, a complicated technological achievement, is a very important step in the understanding of human facial expressions and their role in socialising. What is actually Kismet?", "correct_answer": "A sociable humanoid robot", "incorrect_answers": ["A technique for enhancing the ability of the face to conduct emotions", "A set of tiny devices implanted under the skin, which detect microexpressions", "An advanced computer system, designed to analyze microexpressions"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Appallosa, when the widowed Allison French arrives in Appaloosa, Virgil and Everett help her get this job at the hotel.", "correct_answer": "Piano player", "incorrect_answers": ["Housekeeper", "Prostitute", "Bar maid"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the diet of coyotes?", "correct_answer": "They eat insects.", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "60% of their diet consists of mammals.", "They do not eat prairie dogs."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To find the acceleration of a particle what would we do to the velocity ?", "correct_answer": "Differentiate once", "incorrect_answers": ["Integrate twice", "Differentiate twice", "Integrate once"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which type of blood cells can be stored the longest?", "correct_answer": "Erythrocytes (red blood cells)", "incorrect_answers": ["Platelets", "Blood plasma", "Leukocytes (white blood cells)"]}]